- Let AI help you create, summarize,
and analyze your documents, messages, and data.
Copilot, Microsoft's AI assistant is now available
in Microsoft 365 applications, including Word,
Excel, and Teams as an optional add-on
from Microsoft 365 business and enterprise subscribers.
I'm Nick Brazzi, and I'd like to introduce you
to generating drafts, analyzing spreadsheet data,
creating presentations, and more,
using natural language requests.
Telling Copilot what you want is like having a chat
conversation with a real person.
Copilot can also summarize or answer direct questions
about chat conversations, online meetings,
and email threads.
A quick introduction is all it takes to get started
with Microsoft's AI assistant.